Guide to the Records of the Research Institute for the Study of Man's (RISM) Medical and Social Anthropological Research in Bolivia RISM.RG.8
New York University Archives
- Series XII. Reports from RISM to the Peace Corps, Partial Reports Related to the RISM Bolivia Project, 1964-1967; 1 Linear Feet in 1 record carton
  - Orio Figures and References, undated (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - Zaki Copy: Acknowledgements, References, Epidemiological., undated (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Technological Report on the Epidemiological Study, 1965 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Report #8, September 1966 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Report #4, October 1965 (Box 272, Folder 23)
- Series XIII. Miscellaneous Papers, 1964-2006; 1.1 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  This series consists of 0.5 linear feet, arranged chronologically. This series contains articles, tables, charts and notes that relate to the Project's research goals. Some material is duplicated in Series I. Correspondence.
  - Estudios Socio Economico en las Provincias de Omasuyos, Inganin (sp) y Los Andes, La Paz, 1946 (Box NA, Item 1)
  - Censo General de Bolivia, 1950 (Box NA, Item 2)
  - Monografia Estadistic Indigena de Bolivia with maps, undated (Box NA, Item 3)
  - Bolivia's Adventure in Learning, Natural History, Dec 1954 (Box NA, Item 4)
  - Cuentos Nacionales y Cuadros Estadisticos, 1958-1964 (Box NA, Item 5)
  - CEP Boletin Informativo, Centro de Estudios de Poblacion; Bibliografia de Articulos Sobre Los Indios Bolivianos en Revistas Y Periodicos; population maps, Jul 1959; Oct 1968, undated (Box NA, Item 6)
  - Siles Zuazo, Herman4 Anos de Gob Rev. 1956 - 1960 Bolivia Edit. Del Estado Sin [?] (Box NA, Item 7)
  - Boletin Estadistico, 1960 (Box NA, Item 8)
  - Boletin Estadistico, 1962 (Box NA, Item 9)
  - Boletin Estadistico, 1963 (Box NA, Item 10)
  - Cuadros Estadisticos para la Encuesta Demografia y de Vivienda, Apr 1963 (Box NA, Item 11)
  - V. Paz Estenssoro, Mensage al Congreso, undated (Box NA, Item 12)
  - Journal entry about Peace Corps. workers in Sorata, undated (Box NA, Item 13)
  - Preliminary program for Seminar on Anthropology of the Andes and Its Environs, undated (Box NA, Item 14)
  - Facultad De Servicio Social, undated (Box NA, Item 15)
  - Education references in Bolivia Studyman [?], undated (Box NA, Item 16)
  - Notes: Finot - Sobre El Problema del Indio, undated (Box NA, Item 17)
  - Notes on various Bolivian communities, undated (Box NA, Item 18)
  - Notes, tables and charts, undated (Box NA, Item 19)
  - Tables and charts, undated (Box NA, Item 20)
  - Tables and charts, undated (Box NA, Item 21)
  - Type and content of archives, undated (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Curatorial computer files, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Community study outline, undated (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Promotional materials: Retrospect and Prospect: Preservation and Use of Archival Materials in the Digital Age, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Photocopied materials re: Peace Corps/RISM Bolivia project, 1964-1966 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Bolivia Project General Inventory, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Bolivia Film Strips: U.S. Productions: Legal Correspondence, 1967 (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - Bolivia--Description & Travel, undated (Box 312, Folder 9)
  - Epidemiological Studies in Bolivia: Sorata, Atahuallpani, A1-15, 1964 (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Serology reports, 1965 (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Epidemiological Studies in Bolivia: Reviews, 1972-1975 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - Changing Rural Bolivia: Reviews, 1970-1976 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - Background material on Bolivia, 1946-1968 (Box 313, Folder 1-12)
  - Project summaries and reports, 1965-1969 (Box 313, Folder 13-21)
- Appendix: Computer Cards
  - Name Card: Coroico, undated (Box 319)
  - Name Card: Coroico, Villa Abecia, Reyes, San Miguel, undated (Box 320)
  - Name Card: San Miguel, undated (Box 321)
  - Name Card: Reyes, undated (Box 322)
  - Name Card: Reyes, undated (Box 323)
  - Name Card: Compi, undated (Box 324)
  - Name Card: Unlabeled, undated (Box 325)
  - Name Card: Sorata, San Miguel, undated (Box 326)
  - Unlabeled tab cards, undated (Box 327)
  - Maney 3/5, undated (Box 328)
  - Census Data Cards: Coroico, 1966 (Box 329)
  - Census Data Cards: Coroico, Mururata, Cruz Loma, Sorata, 1966 (Box 330)
  - Census Data Cards: Sorata, Reyes, 1966 (Box 331)
  - Census Data Cards: San Miguel, Llamachchi, 1966 (Box 332)
  - Census Data Cards: Compi, Villa Abecia, 1966 (Box 333)
  - Data Coded Binder: Political Activity, undated (Box 334)
  - Data Coded Binder: Stratification, undated (Box 335)
  - Data Coded Binder: Community Action, undated (Box 336)
  - Data Coded Binder: Group Structure, undated (Box 337)